lrworld.com 2016-07-29

# Privacy Policy | LR Health & Beauty Systems

 Safeguarding your privacy and protecting your personal data are of major importance to us. Lawful and responsible handling of your data is an essential part of our corporate policy. This includes comprehensive information on your saved data. Our aim is to provide you with top confidentiality and security. We herewith inform you about the nature, scope and purpose of collecting and using your personal data. 

  **1\. Collecting personal data  **

We do not collect any personal data via the freely accessible part of this website (no login required) such as name, address, telephone number, email addresses or IP addresses, – except the following: 

**1.1 Input of data in the contact form  **  
Entering your data in the contact forms of this website or submitting your data via email is voluntary. We save and process this data to answer your requests or to provide you with the necessary information. Should you be interested in becoming a partner in the LR sales system, we will save and process your data for the purpose of promotion and implementation of your partner position in the LR sales system and forward them to the respective affiliated companies and sales partners in the LR sales system to enable optimised processing of your request. Should you be interested in becoming a partner abroad, we will forward your data to the respective unit abroad.  

**1.2 Etracker / Cookies  **  
For statistical purposes data is collected and saved on this website using technology from etracker GmbH (www.etracker.com). User profiles are generated from this data under a pseudonym. Cookies may be used for this purpose. Cookies are minor text files which are saved on your computer. Cookies enable recognition of the internet browser. Without the explicit consent of the user, data collected with etracker technology is not used for identifying the visitor of this website and will not be linked to the personal data via the pseudonym carrier. The data saved are exclusively evaluated for statistical purposes; there will be no disclosure to a third party neither for commercial nor for non-commercial use. Collecting and saving data may be repudiated at any time with future effect; you may also change the pre-setting of your browser so that cookies are rejected. 

**1.3 Disclosure to third parties**    
Irrespective of the aforementioned exceptions when entering your data in the contact form, we will not disclose your personal data to third parties. In particular, we will not undertake any address or data trade. Your data will only be processed by us or trustworthy service providers who render IT services to us.  

**2\. Security  **  
We undertake appropriate technical and organisational safety measures to protect your personal data against unsolicited or unlawful deletion, alteration or loss and against unauthorised disclosure or unauthorised access. 

**3\. Links  **  
We are not responsible for sites we link to other companies and persons. The respective privacy policy applies for the handling of your personal data on these websites. 

**4\. Accessing the terms of use  **  
You may access information on data protection on this page at any time. We will publish future alterations regarding our terms of use and data protection information also on this site. The permanent internet address of this site is: www.lrworld.com/en/Datenschutz 

**5\. Do you have any questions or requests?  **  
We look forward to hearing from you with questions and suggestions regarding privacy policy which is very important to us. Please do not hesitate to contact us at datenschutz@lrworld.com 

**LR Health & Beauty Systems GmbH, last amended 01 January 2012  **
